



As a graduate of the University of Melbourne, I am searching for work in technology or design. These areas include product (UX/UI) design, software development or graphic design. Having already gained experience in digital design, frontend software development and architectural design, I have a broad skillset perspective and continue to learn new skills daily.

WORK EXPERIENCE 🖻

EMERSON VISUALS | FREELANCE DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

Melbourne | 2017 - Present

- I create UX/UI and Graphic Design solutions for small businesses.
 I also program responsive websites and web apps for small clients.
- > Some of the organisations I have worked with but are not limited to include the Melbourne International Comedy Festival, the University of Melbourne and the Melbourne Theatre Company.

MCILDOWIE ARCHITECTS | ARCHITECTURE INTERNSHIP

Flinders Lane | 2019 - March 2020

- > Being part of a team of architects to generate a masterplan for a school in Sydney
- > Measuring, 3D modelling and developing various floorplans for a potential house renovation in Dromana.
- > Communicating back to associates for each project at the firm as well as answering calls from engineers / quantity surveyors.

EVENTS PHOTOGRAPHER | POLAR BLUE PHOTOGRAPHY

Melbourne | 2019 - 2022

- > Capturing photos for professional career events such as corporate cocktail nights and university events such as balls.
- > Includes developing and editing the photos prior to finishing the event. This includes fixing colour issues and adding a watermark

HOSPITALITY WORKER | VARIOUS CAFES & RESTAURAUNTS

Melbourne | 2018 - 2021

- > Serving drinks and food to customers. This includes ensuring all items are present for the visitor and are cleaned afterwards.
- > Cooking / making drinks was involved. Communication also made to managers to ensure all safety procedures were followed.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE

Melbourne | 2018 - 2022

> Bachelor of Design | Double major in Architecture & Construction

ST KEVIN'S COLLEGE

Melbourne | 2010 - 2017

> High school completed, class of 2017

AWARDS 8

TOP ARTS VCAA BOARD AWARD

Melbourne | 2018

> \$1000 prize award for Top Arts 2018

MSDX - UNIVERSITY EXHIBITION

Melbourne | 2019

> Architecture work displayed at University

SKILLS @

SOFTWARE

> Illustrator, Indesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, After Effects, Adobe XD, Figma, Rhino 3D, Revit, Procreate, VRAY, Excel, VS Code

CODING LANGUAGES / SKILLS

> HTML, CSS, Javascript, GIT, Wireframing, Prototyping, User Testing, User Research

REFERALS

- > Alex Bartaska | Design Work 0428 004 410
- > Callum Straford | Client 0414 138 836